<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Safi&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://safiuddinkhan.github.io/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Safi&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 12:08:06 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://safiuddinkhan.github.io/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to run SuperTuxKart properly on your Pi4 with Raspberry Pi OS Bullseye (64-bit)</title>
      <link>https://safiuddinkhan.github.io/posts/supertuxkart_pi4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 12:08:06 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://safiuddinkhan.github.io/posts/supertuxkart_pi4/</guid>
      <description>OK, so you install SuperTuxKart on your Pi4 from the repos and find out that it does not run properly and you see missing graphics like in the screenshot and you say to yourself what a piece of crap that it cannot even run SuperTuxKart properly. Well this is because most SBCs including Pi4 have the guts of mobile phone and they mainly support OpenGL ES properly and the implementation of OpenGL 3 is not complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to control the keyboard and mouse of your compute remotely via SSH</title>
      <link>https://safiuddinkhan.github.io/posts/control_keyboard_mouse_ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 09:08:47 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://safiuddinkhan.github.io/posts/control_keyboard_mouse_ssh/</guid>
      <description>In order to control the keyboard and mouse of your computer remotely via SSH follow the following steps.
  SSH into your system with X tunning enabled by putting &amp;quot;-X&amp;quot; flag at the end of your SSH command &amp;ldquo;ssh &amp;lt;user&amp;gt;@&amp;lt;ip_address&amp;gt; -X&amp;rdquo;
  Install x2x package on your remote computer. If you are running Debian/Ubuntu based distro then type &amp;ldquo;sudo apt install x2x&amp;rdquo; on your remote computer to install the package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make Raspberry Pi OS Bullseye more useful</title>
      <link>https://safiuddinkhan.github.io/posts/how_to_make_raspberry_pi_os_more_useful/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 17:48:07 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://safiuddinkhan.github.io/posts/how_to_make_raspberry_pi_os_more_useful/</guid>
      <description>Raspberry Pi OS is great for beginners but after a while you will start to realize that its desktop environment which is a modification of LXDE environment is rather limited to be used as a desktop. To make Raspberry Pi OS into the more standard Debian distro on which it is based on follow the following steps.
 Either select &amp;ldquo;Raspberry Pi OS Lite (64-bit)&amp;quot; or &amp;ldquo;Raspberry Pi OS Lite (32-bit)&amp;quot; and write it on your SD Card or USB Drive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
